<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<God>
	<name>Saradomin</name>
	<age>10000</age>
	<colors>Blue, yellow, white, silver</colors>
	<ascension>Prolonged exposure to multiple Elder Artefacts, beginning with the Crown Archival</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Human</birthRace>
	<description>Presently, Saradomin has a vast number of followers, most of whom believe him to be the god of good,
	 and there are far more churches dedicated to him than to other gods. Most of his modern followers reside in Misthalin, Asgarnia,
	 Kandarin and Entrana, but there are several groups outside these areas. Unlike those of Zamorak or Guthix, his followers consist
	 almost entirely of humans, though that was not always the case. Saradomin's symbol is a four-pointed star 
	 (that is usually coloured gold or silver), which he likely took from his crown. Saradomin was the first god to return to 
	 Gielinor in the Sixth Age, after Guthix's death. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Guthix</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Green</colors>
	<ascension>Killing Skargaroth with his sword, an Elder Artefact</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Human</birthRace>
	<description>He became a god at the end of a war between gods on his realm, which saw the deaths of all his friends and 
	family. By killing the god Skargaroth, he ascended to godhood himself, after which he left his devastated world. 
	Soon afterwards, he discovered Gielinor, and, astonished by its beauty, shaped it to his liking for mortals to live on 
	it without interference from gods. He then populated the world and created runestones for its inhabitants to use, thus 
	earning Gielinor the nickname RuneScape. He descended into a slumber, hoping to be forgotten by his worshippers, but other 
	gods began to arrive in the following centuries, which eventually led to the breaking out of the God Wars. After four 
	millennia of warring, Guthix awoke, ended the wars, and banished all gods, much to their followers' dismay. 
	Nearly twenty-two centuries later, his cave was discovered and Guthix was murdered by the Zarosian Mahjarrat Sliske, shattering 
	the Edicts he put in place after the God Wars. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Zamorak</name>
	<age>10000</age>
	<colors>Red, black, gold </colors>
	<ascension>Obtaining the Stone of Jas and
	defeating Zaros with Staff of Armadyl</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Mahjarrat</birthRace>
	<description>As a mortal, he was an exceptionally powerful warrior, but notably less skilled in magic compared to other 
	Mahjarrat such as Azzanadra or Lucien. As a military genius who was also knowledgeable about Freneskae’s harsh culture, 
	Zamorak assisted in creating a considerable empire in the Second Age, earning the title Legatus Maximus Zamorak the Scourge[1] 
	by Zaros. Although Zamorak is considered as a mystical infatuation of chaos by his followers, he is seen as an evil god by his 
	rivals and their followers. However, there has been a great deal of historical ignorance with respect to the human NPCs of 
	Gielinor who got influenced by Saradomin. Zamorak simply grew tired of the stagnation in the Zarosian empire, already being the 
	most powerful Mahjarrat at that time, followed by Azzanadra [7]. As a result, he betrayed Zaros with a large group of followers, 
	and attained godhood by absorbing the Empty Lord's power by accident after having obtained the Stone of Jas which, in 
	conjunction with the Staff of Armadyl, granted him enough power to do so. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Bandos</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Teal, brown, dark green</colors>
	<ascension>Killing the god Jododu Otoku</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Kal-i-kra tribe</birthRace>
	<description>Having first set foot on Gielinor in the Second Age, he was the patron god of the brutish and unintelligent races 
	such as goblins, trolls,[5] ogres, and orks, most of whom he took with him from their realm Yu'biusk, where he had crossbred 
	them after taking over. Some followers, mostly goblins, refer to him as the Big High War God 
	(with the exception of priests on holy days,[1] although goblins native to Gielinor do not take this rule to heart[6]). 
	He was almost completely forgotten by the humans of Gielinor due to his disappearance after the God Wars until his battle 
	against Armadyl in the early Sixth Age, which ended with his death.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Armadyl</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Pale blue, silver, amber, gold</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Giant</birthRace>
	<description>Armadyl was one of the major participants in the Gielinorian God Wars. Although the God Wars destroyed most of the 
	aviantese, some of their warriors can still be found within the God Wars Dungeon, led by Armadyl's aviansie general, Kree'arra. 
	The god left Gielinor at the end of the wars to roam the cosmos, mourning his lost kin; as a consequence, he had relatively 
	little activity in Gielinor after the end of the God Wars, and he is not as well-known as Saradomin, Guthix and Zamorak, nor did 
	he have a substantial following before the beginning of the Sixth Age.  Shortly after the death of Guthix Armadyl returned to 
	Gielinor. He desires global safety and justice for his following.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Zaros</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Purple, Black, Gold</colors>
	<ascension>Chosen by Elder Gods</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Incorporeal</birthRace>
	<description>Unlike the young gods, Zaros was never a mortal; he has never been anything else but a divine being. 
	Zaros and Seren were both created by the Elder God Mah on Freneskae when the last cycle of the universe began, 
	what Zaros describes as eons ago, to serve as company. They were tied to each other in ways neither could control. 
	It was a mutual "attraction" of sorts that weakened Zaros' concentration and Seren's will in order to bring them together. 
	Mah, with the temperament of a child due to a lack of anima - thus making her a purely instinctual being without memory or 
	knowledge - saw them as her "playthings", in a sense. However, Zaros resented this. Unable to learn anything from his creator, 
	he longed to escape and create his own destiny. Seren, on the other hand, felt it was their duty to remain with Mah. 
	She felt that Mah needed them and only created them out of the fear of being alone. Zaros abandoned both Mah and Seren. 
	He set out to search the stars for whatever he would find. The first world he came to was that of Infernus. 
	Zaros wants the world to belong to mortals, similarly to Guthix, but believes that mortals would neither be safe nor capable 
	of living without the guidance of gods, who are able to set some rules and exercise proper control; otherwise, 
	everything would turn to chaos. As such, he suggests that he watches mortals silently, making checks and balances to 
	ensure 'balance' is maintained, and to silently guide mortals to fulfil their greatest potential and protect them from 
	themselves and the Elder Gods. He strives to become an Elder God himself for it would be the only way for him to communicate 
	with them, allowing him to attempt to stop them from destroying mortal life.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Seren</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Cyan</colors>
	<ascension>Chosen by Elder Gods</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Devine Ice Crystal</birthRace>
	<description>Seren, along with Zaros, was created by the Elder God Mah. Where Seren represents light, Zaros represents darkness: 
	this binds the two and compels them to each other when in close proximity. When Zaros and Seren are near each other, 
	they are charmed by each other, which Zaros thinks is controlled by Mah. Seren is described by Zaros to be driven more by 
	emotion, whilst Zaros by logical reasoning. She had a close relationship with the god of balance, Guthix, who brought her to 
	Gielinor from Tarddiad during the First Age through the World Gate, along with the elves. They settled in Tirannwn and built 
	the great city of Prifddinas which is the oldest surviving settlement on Gielinor. As some of her beloved elves began to die of 
	old age Seren became resolved in extending their lifespans. She did so, but at a cost: inexplicably tying them to her. 
	When outside of her presence for too long the elves would become sick and feverish, eventually dying. Seren describes this 
	as her greatest mistake.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Skargaroth</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>None</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Skargaroth was an ancient and powerful god who contributed to the extinction of the Naragi and the destruction 
	of Guthix's homeworld. During the late Naragun God Wars, Skargaroth battled the goddess Tuska and her armies, and was impaled 
	before falling on top of a house. His weight destroyed the house, and Guthix's daughter Aagi, who was hiding inside, was killed 
	with it. In retaliation, Guthix stabbed Skargaroth in his back with Skargaroth's own elder sword, which killed him and transferred 
	his power and part of his knowledge to Guthix. Guthix then ascended into godhood. Skargaroth's dead form is seen as an empty and 
	hollow shell of his body in Guthix's memory at the end of The World Wakes.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Tuska</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Teal and possibly purple and grey.</colors>
	<ascension>Killing a god</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Tuska was a boar-like goddess who attacked Naragun during the Naragi God Wars. She fought against Saradomin, 
	eventually making him move to another realm due to the disruption she caused. Tuska is described as a mindless beast that has 
	managed to attain godhood. Since Tuska was a formidable foe, her presence attracted Skargaroth to hunt her down. During a fight 
	between Tuska and Skargaroth, Guthix used the elder god sword he had found to severely wound Tuska by stabbing her in the eye, 
	making her completely blind. Tuska finally met her demise at the hand of Vorago, after having attempted to invade 
	and devour Gielinor.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Brassica Prime</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Green, gold</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Cabbage</birthRace>
	<description>Brassica Prime is the cheerful patron god of all cabbages and, as such, takes the form of a giant cabbage. 
	He claims to command the power of highly concentrated nutrients. Likely due to being a giant vegetable, 
	Brassica Prime believes that power comes from deliciousness, probably due to the fact that most fruits and vegetables 
	wish to be eaten to spread their seeds around, and thus the more deliciousness, the more chance of being picked and propagating.
	Brassica was involved in the 2007 April Fools event, the 2009 April Fools event, and makes small appearances in The Death of 
	Chivalry and Missing, Presumed Death. He also features in the Cabbage Facepunch Bonanza with the monkey goddess of parties, 
	Marimbo, and briefly appeared for Sliske's Endgame.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Marimbo</name>
	<age>5000</age>
	<colors>Brown, Yellow</colors>
	<ascension>Unintentionally killing a god in a drinking contest with the Elder Horn.</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Gorilla</birthRace>
	<description>Marimbo is the ancient and cheeky matron goddess of monkeys. At some point, she went to Ape Atoll in search of 
	followers. There she found monkeys; she may or may not have granted them their intelligence. Marimbo decided to stay on 
	Ape Atoll, and the monkeys there still worship her to this day. Once the Edicts of Guthix were established, Marimbo was 
	forced to leave Gielinor and, according to Mod Osborne, because Marimbo is a light-hearted character she partied once the 
	Third Age ended and the Edicts were introduced. This contrasts with the other gods, who were not happy to leave. The town 
	Marim, on the island of Ape Atoll, is named after her and her only known place of worship is the temple there. Large statues of 
	Marimbo sit inside the Temple of Marimbo on Ape Atoll. Players may see them next to the altar on the first floor of the building. 
	The statues depict her as a giant gorilla. Her symbol is a triangle (or diamond) which points downwards, with a vertical spike 
	hanging from the bottom point.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name></name>
	<age></age>
	<colors></colors>
	<ascension></ascension>
	<gender></gender>
	<birthRace></birthRace>
	<description></description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID></tierID>
</God>