<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<God>
	<name>Saradomin</name>
	<age>10000</age>
	<colors>Blue, yellow, white, silver</colors>
	<ascension>Prolonged exposure to multiple Elder Artefacts, beginning with the Crown Archival</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Human</birthRace>
	<description>Presently, Saradomin has a vast number of followers, most of whom believe him to be the god of good,
	 and there are far more churches dedicated to him than to other gods. Most of his modern followers reside in Misthalin, Asgarnia,
	 Kandarin and Entrana, but there are several groups outside these areas. Unlike those of Zamorak or Guthix, his followers consist
	 almost entirely of humans, though that was not always the case. Saradomin's symbol is a four-pointed star 
	 (that is usually coloured gold or silver), which he likely took from his crown. Saradomin was the first god to return to 
	 Gielinor in the Sixth Age, after Guthix's death. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>3</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Guthix</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Green</colors>
	<ascension>Killing Skargaroth with his sword, an Elder Artefact</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Human</birthRace>
	<description>He became a god at the end of a war between gods on his realm, which saw the deaths of all his friends and 
	family. By killing the god Skargaroth, he ascended to godhood himself, after which he left his devastated world. 
	Soon afterwards, he discovered Gielinor, and, astonished by its beauty, shaped it to his liking for mortals to live on 
	it without interference from gods. He then populated the world and created runestones for its inhabitants to use, thus 
	earning Gielinor the nickname RuneScape. He descended into a slumber, hoping to be forgotten by his worshippers, but other 
	gods began to arrive in the following centuries, which eventually led to the breaking out of the God Wars. After four 
	millennia of warring, Guthix awoke, ended the wars, and banished all gods, much to their followers' dismay. 
	Nearly twenty-two centuries later, his cave was discovered and Guthix was murdered by the Zarosian Mahjarrat Sliske, shattering 
	the Edicts he put in place after the God Wars. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>2</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Zamorak</name>
	<age>10000</age>
	<colors>Red, black, gold </colors>
	<ascension>Obtaining the Stone of Jas and
	defeating Zaros with Staff of Armadyl</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Mahjarrat</birthRace>
	<description>As a mortal, he was an exceptionally powerful warrior, but notably less skilled in magic compared to other 
	Mahjarrat such as Azzanadra or Lucien. As a military genius who was also knowledgeable about Freneskae’s harsh culture, 
	Zamorak assisted in creating a considerable empire in the Second Age, earning the title Legatus Maximus Zamorak the Scourge[1] 
	by Zaros. Although Zamorak is considered as a mystical infatuation of chaos by his followers, he is seen as an evil god by his 
	rivals and their followers. However, there has been a great deal of historical ignorance with respect to the human NPCs of 
	Gielinor who got influenced by Saradomin. Zamorak simply grew tired of the stagnation in the Zarosian empire, already being the 
	most powerful Mahjarrat at that time, followed by Azzanadra [7]. As a result, he betrayed Zaros with a large group of followers, 
	and attained godhood by absorbing the Empty Lord's power by accident after having obtained the Stone of Jas which, in 
	conjunction with the Staff of Armadyl, granted him enough power to do so. </description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>5</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Bandos</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Teal, brown, dark green</colors>
	<ascension>Killing the god Jododu Otoku</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Kal-i-kra tribe</birthRace>
	<description>Having first set foot on Gielinor in the Second Age, he was the patron god of the brutish and unintelligent races 
	such as goblins, trolls,[5] ogres, and orks, most of whom he took with him from their realm Yu'biusk, where he had crossbred 
	them after taking over. Some followers, mostly goblins, refer to him as the Big High War God 
	(with the exception of priests on holy days,[1] although goblins native to Gielinor do not take this rule to heart[6]). 
	He was almost completely forgotten by the humans of Gielinor due to his disappearance after the God Wars until his battle 
	against Armadyl in the early Sixth Age, which ended with his death.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>4</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Armadyl</name>
	<age>11000</age>
	<colors>Pale blue, silver, amber, gold</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Giant</birthRace>
	<description>Armadyl was one of the major participants in the Gielinorian God Wars. Although the God Wars destroyed most of the 
	aviantese, some of their warriors can still be found within the God Wars Dungeon, led by Armadyl's aviansie general, Kree'arra. 
	The god left Gielinor at the end of the wars to roam the cosmos, mourning his lost kin; as a consequence, he had relatively 
	little activity in Gielinor after the end of the God Wars, and he is not as well-known as Saradomin, Guthix and Zamorak, nor did 
	he have a substantial following before the beginning of the Sixth Age.  Shortly after the death of Guthix Armadyl returned to 
	Gielinor. He desires global safety and justice for his following.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>4</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Zaros</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Purple, Black, Gold</colors>
	<ascension>Chosen by Elder Gods</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Incorporeal</birthRace>
	<description>Unlike the young gods, Zaros was never a mortal; he has never been anything else but a divine being. 
	Zaros and Seren were both created by the Elder God Mah on Freneskae when the last cycle of the universe began, 
	what Zaros describes as eons ago, to serve as company. They were tied to each other in ways neither could control. 
	It was a mutual "attraction" of sorts that weakened Zaros' concentration and Seren's will in order to bring them together. 
	Mah, with the temperament of a child due to a lack of anima - thus making her a purely instinctual being without memory or 
	knowledge - saw them as her "playthings", in a sense. However, Zaros resented this. Unable to learn anything from his creator, 
	he longed to escape and create his own destiny. Seren, on the other hand, felt it was their duty to remain with Mah. 
	She felt that Mah needed them and only created them out of the fear of being alone. Zaros abandoned both Mah and Seren. 
	He set out to search the stars for whatever he would find. The first world he came to was that of Infernus. 
	Zaros wants the world to belong to mortals, similarly to Guthix, but believes that mortals would neither be safe nor capable 
	of living without the guidance of gods, who are able to set some rules and exercise proper control; otherwise, 
	everything would turn to chaos. As such, he suggests that he watches mortals silently, making checks and balances to 
	ensure 'balance' is maintained, and to silently guide mortals to fulfil their greatest potential and protect them from 
	themselves and the Elder Gods. He strives to become an Elder God himself for it would be the only way for him to communicate 
	with them, allowing him to attempt to stop them from destroying mortal life.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>2</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Seren</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Cyan</colors>
	<ascension>Chosen by Elder Gods</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Devine Ice Crystal</birthRace>
	<description>Seren, along with Zaros, was created by the Elder God Mah. Where Seren represents light, Zaros represents darkness: 
	this binds the two and compels them to each other when in close proximity. When Zaros and Seren are near each other, 
	they are charmed by each other, which Zaros thinks is controlled by Mah. Seren is described by Zaros to be driven more by 
	emotion, whilst Zaros by logical reasoning. She had a close relationship with the god of balance, Guthix, who brought her to 
	Gielinor from Tarddiad during the First Age through the World Gate, along with the elves. They settled in Tirannwn and built 
	the great city of Prifddinas which is the oldest surviving settlement on Gielinor. As some of her beloved elves began to die of 
	old age Seren became resolved in extending their lifespans. She did so, but at a cost: inexplicably tying them to her. 
	When outside of her presence for too long the elves would become sick and feverish, eventually dying. Seren describes this 
	as her greatest mistake.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>2</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Skargaroth</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>None</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Skargaroth was an ancient and powerful god who contributed to the extinction of the Naragi and the destruction 
	of Guthix's homeworld. During the late Naragun God Wars, Skargaroth battled the goddess Tuska and her armies, and was impaled 
	before falling on top of a house. His weight destroyed the house, and Guthix's daughter Aagi, who was hiding inside, was killed 
	with it. In retaliation, Guthix stabbed Skargaroth in his back with Skargaroth's own elder sword, which killed him and transferred 
	his power and part of his knowledge to Guthix. Guthix then ascended into godhood. Skargaroth's dead form is seen as an empty and 
	hollow shell of his body in Guthix's memory at the end of The World Wakes.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>4</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Tuska</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Teal and possibly purple and grey.</colors>
	<ascension>Killing a god</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Tuska was a boar-like goddess who attacked Naragun during the Naragi God Wars. She fought against Saradomin, 
	eventually making him move to another realm due to the disruption she caused. Tuska is described as a mindless beast that has 
	managed to attain godhood. Since Tuska was a formidable foe, her presence attracted Skargaroth to hunt her down. During a fight 
	between Tuska and Skargaroth, Guthix used the elder god sword he had found to severely wound Tuska by stabbing her in the eye, 
	making her completely blind. Tuska finally met her demise at the hand of Vorago, after having attempted to invade 
	and devour Gielinor.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>4</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Brassica Prime</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Green, gold</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Cabbage</birthRace>
	<description>Brassica Prime is the cheerful patron god of all cabbages and, as such, takes the form of a giant cabbage. 
	He claims to command the power of highly concentrated nutrients. Likely due to being a giant vegetable, 
	Brassica Prime believes that power comes from deliciousness, probably due to the fact that most fruits and vegetables 
	wish to be eaten to spread their seeds around, and thus the more deliciousness, the more chance of being picked and propagating.
	Brassica was involved in the 2007 April Fools event, the 2009 April Fools event, and makes small appearances in The Death of 
	Chivalry and Missing, Presumed Death. He also features in the Cabbage Facepunch Bonanza with the monkey goddess of parties, 
	Marimbo, and briefly appeared for Sliske's Endgame.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>5</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Marimbo</name>
	<age>5000</age>
	<colors>Brown, Yellow</colors>
	<ascension>Unintentionally killing a god in a drinking contest with the Elder Horn.</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Gorilla</birthRace>
	<description>Marimbo is the ancient and cheeky matron goddess of monkeys. At some point, she went to Ape Atoll in search of 
	followers. There she found monkeys; she may or may not have granted them their intelligence. Marimbo decided to stay on 
	Ape Atoll, and the monkeys there still worship her to this day. Once the Edicts of Guthix were established, Marimbo was 
	forced to leave Gielinor and, according to Mod Osborne, because Marimbo is a light-hearted character she partied once the 
	Third Age ended and the Edicts were introduced. This contrasts with the other gods, who were not happy to leave. The town 
	Marim, on the island of Ape Atoll, is named after her and her only known place of worship is the temple there. Large statues of 
	Marimbo sit inside the Temple of Marimbo on Ape Atoll. Players may see them next to the altar on the first floor of the building. 
	The statues depict her as a giant gorilla. Her symbol is a triangle (or diamond) which points downwards, with a vertical spike 
	hanging from the bottom point.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>5</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Elidinis</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Yellow and turquoise</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Elidinis is the Menaphite Goddess of Fertility and Growth, and is heavily associated with the River Elid. 
	She is also the wife of Tumeken, the mother of Icthlarin and Amascut, and one of the four major gods of the Menaphite Pantheon. 
	She plays a key part of the quest Spirits of the Elid. She is described by Senliten as "The water that gives life and soothes". 
	Elidinis is mainly worshipped by the peoples of the desert. The centre of her worship is the town of Nardah. In Nardah, 
	there is a shrine to Elidinis (Elidinis Statuette), provided by the god herself to Nardarine, a refugee of the God Wars, 
	who went on to found and lead Nardah. Like most of the other gods, she was forced to leave after the God Wars due to the 
	Edicts of Guthix.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>5</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Tumeken</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Yellow and Grey</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Tumeken, sometimes referred to in Menaphite texts as the Lord of Light and the God of 
	the Sun, is the god of light, the husband of Elidinis, the father of Icthlarin and Amascut, one of the four major gods of the 
	Menaphite Pantheon and co-founder of Kharidian. He is also responsible for using a piece of his essence to create the four 
	minor gods of the pantheon, Het, Crondis, Apmeken, and Scabaras. Because of this, Tumeken is directly or indirectly responsible 
	for creating a majority of the desert pantheon and can be seen as its leader, though he has not been active 
	since the Second Age.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>5</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Amascut</name>
	<age>300</age>
	<colors>Cerise, gold and jade</colors>
	<ascension>Infused with divine energy from Tumeken and Elidinis</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Demigod</birthRace>
	<description>Amascut, also known as "The Devourer", is the goddess of destruction and one of the four major gods of the 
	Menaphite Pantheon, a family of deities that rule over the Kharidian Desert. She is the daughter of Tumeken and Elidinis and 
	a sister to Icthlarin, another member of the Pantheon. Amascut is often depicted as a lioness-headed woman. Amascut plays the 
	role of the desert quest series's primary antagonist, spreading chaos and terror, such as by devouring the Sophanem 
	High Priest's soul and stealing the Kharid-ib, an ancient, powerful diamond. She was also featured in the Hallowe'en 2015 
	event alongside Icthlarin and Death.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>6</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Icthlarin</name>
	<age>300</age>
	<colors>Ochre</colors>
	<ascension>Infused with divine energy from Tumeken and Elidinis</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Dog(Demigod)</birthRace>
	<description>Icthlarin is the Menaphite god of the dead, son of Tumeken and Elidinis, and brother of Amascut, the Devourer, 
	and one of the four major gods of the Desert Pantheon. He was the original leader of the Mahjarrat when they first came to 
	Gielinor. His role as a god is not concerned with the act of death, but with the caretaking of the dead, ensuring that the 
	souls reach the afterlife. Icthlarin's only act is to help the spirits of the dead pass through the Grim Underworld safely so 
	they can reach the afterlife where they can rest peacefully in their next life. His task is impeded by his sister, however, 
	because Amascut's goal is to destroy and consume the souls of the dead before they reach the underworld so they are erased 
	completely. To this end, he is important in the funeral rites of those who worship him. This role as a protector of souls often 
	brings Icthlarin into conflict with his sister goddess. He was featured in Hallowe'en 2015 event alongside with Death 
	and Amascut. Cats are guardians of Icthlarin, as Amascut is terrified of them, and as the Sphinx protects the cats, so too does 
	Icthlarin protect the Sphinx.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>6</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Scabaras</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Beige, Dark Blue</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Scabaras is one of the four minor gods of the Menaphite Pantheon, associated with isolation and tranquillity. 
	Due to his nature, little is known of him, and since the banishment of The Sect of Scabaras, his following has diminished 
	greatly. He is usually depicted as a scarab or insect-like humanoid.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>7</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Het</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Unknown</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Male</gender>
	<birthRace>Unknown</birthRace>
	<description>Het is the desert god of health, both physical and mental, and is one of the four minor gods of the Menaphite 
	Pantheon. A manifestation of Het can appear by picking up a canopic jar from Icthlarin's Little Helper. Het is probably the 
	most worshipped of the minor Kharidian Desert gods, with great followings in each of the desert settlements. Al Kharid is 
	particularity notable for this, with a majority of its citizens, such as Ozan, worshipping Het. In the early days, Tumeken had 
	a dream where he wandered the desert, trying to find himself anew. He first travelled north, to a place called Al Kharid, 
	finding many people weak and weary from desert life. When he reached the mountains surrounding Al Kharid, he saw a man holding 
	the pass open, the physical representation of perfection. Tumeken was impressed by this and so gave the man some of his essence, 
	turning him into Het.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>7</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Crondis</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Unknown</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Crocodile</birthRace>
	<description>Crondis is a goddess with the head of a crocodile and the body of a woman. She is one of the four minor gods of 
	the Menaphite Pantheon, and her following is particularly strong in Menaphos and Sophanem. However, as she is rarely spoken of, 
	little is known of her. During Tumeken's Dream, he travelled to Ullek, hoping to see how devout they were. When he arrived, 
	they arranged a feast, and he saw them as excessive and wasteful. He left the the city dispirited and headed into the nearby 
	swamp, where he saw a crocodile capture and kill only enough to feed herself. Tumeken, impressed by this resourcefulness, 
	gave her a piece of himself, turning her into the goddess Crondis.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>7</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Apmeken</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Unknown</colors>
	<ascension>Unknown</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>Human</birthRace>
	<description>pmeken is the goddess of social pleasures, and is one of the four minor gods of the Menaphite Pantheon, 
	a collection of deities that rule over the Kharidian Desert. Her following, as a result, is limited mainly to the desert areas, 
	although the Menaphites of Sophanem follow her most devoutly. Little is known of Apmeken, as she is rarely spoken of, even in 
	Sophanem. During Tumeken's Dream, he travelled westward, towards two camps. He found them at bitter odds with one another, 
	arguing over everything. There were some monkeys nearby who were helping and playing with one another. He called out to them 
	and one of the monkeys scrambled over, climbing onto his shoulder. He praised her joyous and social nature, giving her a part 
	of himself and turning her into Apmeken.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>7</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Avatar of Bandos</name>
	<age>Unknown</age>
	<colors>Unknown(Ice)</colors>
	<ascension>None</ascension>
	<gender>None</gender>
	<birthRace>None</birthRace>
	<description>The Bandos avatar is the final boss of The Chosen Commander quest. It is the Goblin High Priest Bighead with 
	the amulet of Bandos while being under his control. When the high priest took Bandos' pendant and equipped it, he became 
	Bandos' avatar, since most of his power was in the pendant. In order to win against the avatar, you will have to shoot him 
	with Zanik's crossbow. However, during the fight, the crossbow gets broken into three pieces, and needs to be reassembled 
	again to work properly. After you defeat him the second time using the special crossbow is a dialogue option. However, if you 
	do not follow the proper dialogue, he will use his powers to restore all of his health, making him technically immortal.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>7</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Jas</name>
	<age>None</age>
	<colors>White and cream</colors>
	<ascension>Elder God</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>God</birthRace>
	<description>Jas is the oldest and most powerful of the Elder Gods, the ancient beings responsible for the creation of the 
	universe, including Gielinor itself. She is described by a TokHaar-Hok as "time, and so time passes. She is sand, 
	and so there is desert." It has been said that the Elder Gods do not specifically represent an element or aspect, but Jas 
	is most aligned with progression and time, and also has an association with sand and air. In addition to the roles she played 
	in shaping the universe, Jas is specifically responsible for creating almost all of the Elder Artefacts using the Stone of Jas, 
	the first artefact and the one that "most purely expressed her power," and one that has played a prominent role in Gielinor's 
	history. As Mah was thought stillborn, Jas created the Catalyst and the other artefacts to fill the gap Mah left. 
	The Catalyst's purpose was effectively to duplicate Mah's power. Normally, the Elder Gods work together when creating planes. 
	With Mah gone however, each Elder God started creating their own planes in an effort to learn the knowledge lost by Mah's 
	absence, while also destroying the planes from the previous cycle. Jas, with the Stone in her possession, came upon the 
	Dragonkin homeworld, and prepared to destroy it. The Dragonkin tried in vain to take and use the Stone against her. Jas, 
	seeing that life desired power, bound the Dragonkin to the Stone, so that they would no longer desire it.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>1</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Ful</name>
	<age>None</age>
	<colors>Red</colors>
	<ascension>Elder God</ascension>
	<gender>Female</gender>
	<birthRace>God</birthRace>
	<description>Ful is the Elder Goddess of Constancy and Fire. She is the creator of the Elder Kiln and the TokHaar race, 
	and before the translation of the book written by a member of that race, nothing was known about Ful. She is the second 
	oldest Elder God, as well as the second most powerful. Ful and her fellow Elder Gods created many planets in the multiverse; 
	they created them successively in an attempt to create a perfect one. They originally created with their bare hands, but after 
	many failures, created powerful artefacts to aid them and enhance their powers. Ful had created the Elder Kiln, and the TokHaar 
	were created from it to build and shape mountains and planets. When the Elder Gods found the world they created to be imperfect, 
	they would take their artefacts and abandon it. With each failure and experience, the gods and their artefacts — Ful, The Elder 
	Kiln, the TokHaar — grew more skillful in creating worlds.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>1</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Wen</name>
	<age>None</age>
	<colors>Blue</colors>
	<ascension>Elder God</ascension>
	<gender>None</gender>
	<birthRace>God</birthRace>
	<description>Wen is one of the Elder Gods, the ancient beings responsible for the creation of the universe, including Gielinor 
	itself. She is also the Elder God that is related to ice and the cold. She is the third oldest Elder God, as well as the third 
	most powerful. According to Mod Rowley, her facet of time is Inversion. As her chronicle is found atop Ice Mountain, Wen may 
	either reside underneath or could even be the mountain.  Wen may perhaps rest under both the Ice Mountain and the White Wolf 
	Mountain, either broken in two somehow or being so large she also rests under everything in between these mountains. This is 
	hypothesized by Azzanadra when talking to him about Elder Gods after completing Heart of Stone and The Temple at Senntisten. 
	This is because Wen's Elder chronicle and WenKra are tied to Wen in some way and The Measure, being an Elder Artefact, would 
	not be lying about Wen's location.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>1</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Bik</name>
	<age>None</age>
	<colors>Brown and green</colors>
	<ascension>Elder God</ascension>
	<gender>None</gender>
	<birthRace>God</birthRace>
	<description>Bik is one of the five Elder Gods, the ancient beings responsible for the creation of the universe, including 
	Gielinor itself. She is the Elder God related to the forest and trees, and is the second youngest Elder God, as well as the 
	second weakest. After Fate of the Gods, the locations of all the current Elder Gods on Gielinor may be revealed through elder 
	chronicles, which can be found using The Measure. Bik resides underneath Entrana, where her Elder chronicle is found. 
	In Heart of Stone the player visits Entrana again in search of the place where Bik is resting. Instead, they find a mouthpiece, 
	BikKra, that speaks for the elder god. Upon arrival, BikKra challenges the player with three level 35 BikKra's attendants. 
	After defeating all three, they may then speak with BikKra.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>1</tierID>
</God>
<God>
	<name>Mah</name>
	<age>None</age>
	<colors>Purple and Black</colors>
	<ascension>Elder God</ascension>
	<gender>None</gender>
	<birthRace>God</birthRace>
	<description>"Mother" Mah was the youngest of the Elder Gods, as well as the weakest, and was responsible for creating 
	Zaros, Seren, the Mahjarrat tribe, and the Muspah, and was the only known Elder God to have deliberately created life for 
	purposes other than protecting Elder Artefacts or building worlds. She also created the Mahkorat, Mahserrat and Chelon-Mah 
	tribes, although the Mahjarrat came first. Wahisietel (as Ali the Wise) first mentioned her in Tale of the Muspah as a "cruel 
	and archaic creator-god" who created the Muspah, which is further elaborated on in Wahisietel's memory from the Mahjarrat 
	Memories miniquest. Mah makes her first appearance in Fate of the Gods, first dormant on the Freneskae volcano but awakening 
	eventually after Zaros has been reincarnated. She later appears in Children of Mah where she meets her demise.</description>
	<image></image>
	<tierID>1</tierID>
</God>